<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<LanguageData>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.UseMinimumTradeThresholdLabel>Enforce minimum trade value threshold</RealisticOrbitalTrade.UseMinimumTradeThresholdLabel>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.UseMinimumTradeThresholdTooltip>Does it really make sense for an orbital trader and their crew to spend the time, fuel and energy it takes to send down two shuttles all for the sake of a single, cheap trade item? Enabling this and setting a threshold value below makes it so the traders won't accept trades that involves an exchange worth less than the threshold.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.UseMinimumTradeThresholdTooltip>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinimumTradeThresholdLabel>Minimum trade value threshold baseline</RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinimumTradeThresholdLabel>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinimumTradeVariationLabel>Minimum trade value threshold variation: {0}%</RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinimumTradeVariationLabel>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinimumTradeVariationTooltip>For each trader, a random value up to {0}% of the baseline is calculated and either added to or subtracted from the baseline threshold to give the threshold some variation.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinimumTradeVariationTooltip>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.ActiveTradePausesDepartureTimerLabel>Active trade agreement pauses trade ship departure timer</RealisticOrbitalTrade.ActiveTradePausesDepartureTimerLabel>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.ActiveTradePausesDepartureTimerTooltip>By default (when this option is not enabled), the departure timer for the orbital trader continues ticking even during an active trade. However, when this option is enabled, an active trade pauses the timer, allowing you to take all the time you need to complete your trades.\n\nNOTE: The setting's value is applied to a trade agreement upon initiation. Therefore, altering this value won't impact ongoing trades; it will take effect only when you initiate your next trade.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.ActiveTradePausesDepartureTimerTooltip>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.NoEffectWhenActiveTradePausesDepartureIsEnabled>The settings below have no effect when the "Active trade agreement pauses trade ship departure timer" setting is enabled.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.NoEffectWhenActiveTradePausesDepartureIsEnabled>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinTimeUntilDepartureBeforeGraceTimeLabel>Minimum time until departure before adding grace time: {0} hours</RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinTimeUntilDepartureBeforeGraceTimeLabel>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinTimeUntilDepartureBeforeGraceTimeTooltip>If a trade is made when there is less time left before an orbital trader leaves than this setting, the orbital trader will extend their stay with an additional amount of time configurable below. For the sake of balance, the orbital trader will still stop accepting new trades once the original departure time is reached.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.MinTimeUntilDepartureBeforeGraceTimeTooltip>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.DepartureGraceTimeLabel>Grace time added if below minimum time: {0} hours</RealisticOrbitalTrade.DepartureGraceTimeLabel>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.DepartureGraceTimeTooltip>If a trade is made when there is less time left before an orbital trader leaves than the amount of time configurable above, the orbital trader will extend their stay with this additional amount of time. For the sake of balance, the orbital trader will still stop accepting new trades once the original departure time is reached.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.DepartureGraceTimeTooltip>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradersMinimumTradeThreshold>The minimum amount of trade item value this trader is willing to trade for</RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradersMinimumTradeThreshold>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.CurrentTradeValue>The current value of the items you have chosen to trade</RealisticOrbitalTrade.CurrentTradeValue>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeValueDifference>The difference between the current value of the items you have chosen to trade and the minimum value required by the trader. The value is negative and yellow when it's lower than required, and positive and green otherwise.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeValueDifference>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeValue>trade value</RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeValue>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeValueTip>This row shows the status of the trader's minimum trade treshold compared to your current trade value. See the other tips on the numeric values for more information.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeValueTip>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeLessThanMinimumTradeThreshold>The trader is rejecting this trade because the total value of the traded items ({0}) is less than the enforced minimum trade value threshold ({1})</RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeLessThanMinimumTradeThreshold>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.NotAnsweringForGraceTime>{0} is only waiting around to finish an already started agreement and is not interesting in initiating any new trades.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.NotAnsweringForGraceTime>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.NotAnsweringForActiveTrade>{0} reminds you to finish up your current trade agreement before starting another.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.NotAnsweringForActiveTrade>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.RequiredThings>Required specific items</RealisticOrbitalTrade.RequiredThings>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.CancelTradeAgreementLabel>Cancel trade agreement</RealisticOrbitalTrade.CancelTradeAgreementLabel>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.CancelTradeAgreementDesc>Cancels the trade agreement associated with this shuttle. Any partially loaded items will be unloaded first, then the shuttle will leave.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.CancelTradeAgreementDesc>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.NotAnsweringForActiveAmendment>{0} reminds you that you're already in the middle of amending your blacklisting status.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.NotAnsweringForActiveAmendment>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayBlacklistRemovalFeeDialogText>You were blacklisted from trading with orbital traders for destroying one of our shuttles. In order to have your good standing with us reinstated, you will have to pay us back for the parts it takes to produce a shuttle plus the cost of the labor, and finally we charge a nominal fee for the inconvenience you have caused us. The fixed costs are:\n\n{0}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayBlacklistRemovalFeeDialogText>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.LaborCost>Labor: {0}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.LaborCost>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.NominalFeeCost>Nominal fee: {0} (1% of player wealth)</RealisticOrbitalTrade.NominalFeeCost>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.CostOfParts>You've chosen to pay us back in the following manner:</RealisticOrbitalTrade.CostOfParts>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayForWith>{0}: {1}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayForWith>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayWith.Parts>Returning</RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayWith.Parts>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayWith.Silver>Paying for with {0}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayWith.Silver>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.HowPayForParts>How would you like to pay for the {0}?</RealisticOrbitalTrade.HowPayForParts>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayForPartsWithParts>Return the {0}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayForPartsWithParts>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayForPartsWithSilver>Pay for the {0} ({1})</RealisticOrbitalTrade.PayForPartsWithSilver>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.AreYouReadyToPay>You've made your choices, are you ready to pay us back?</RealisticOrbitalTrade.AreYouReadyToPay>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.IAmReadyToPay>I'm ready</RealisticOrbitalTrade.IAmReadyToPay>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.ResetPaymentChoices>I'd like to choose differently</RealisticOrbitalTrade.ResetPaymentChoices>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.CancelAmendmentLabel>Cancel amendment offer
    </RealisticOrbitalTrade.CancelAmendmentLabel>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.CancelAmendmentDesc>Cancels the amendment offer associated with this shuttle. Any partially loaded items will be unloaded first, then the shuttle will leave.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.CancelAmendmentDesc>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.UntilCommsCloseForTrade>({0} until comms close for trade)</RealisticOrbitalTrade.UntilCommsCloseForTrade>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.CommsClosedForTrade>(comms closed for trade)</RealisticOrbitalTrade.CommsClosedForTrade>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.InvolvedInTradeWithInspectString>Involved in orbital trade with {0}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.InvolvedInTradeWithInspectString>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.ActiveTradeShuttle>Trade shuttle waiting to be loaded</RealisticOrbitalTrade.ActiveTradeShuttle>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeShuttleDepartsIn>Trade shuttle departs in {0}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeShuttleDepartsIn>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeShuttleDepartsOn>Trade shuttle involved in orbital trade with {0} departs on {{0}}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeShuttleDepartsOn>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeShuttleRequires>The quest {0} requires you to load the following people or items onto the shuttle:\n{1}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.TradeShuttleRequires>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.QuestPartShuttleLeaveDelay>Trade shuttle leaving in {0}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.QuestPartShuttleLeaveDelay>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.QuestPartShuttleLeaveDelayDesc>The trade shuttle will leave in {1}. The quest {0} requires you to load the following people or items onto the shuttle before it leaves:\n{2}</RealisticOrbitalTrade.QuestPartShuttleLeaveDelayDesc> 146: <RealisticOrbitalTrade.QuestPartShuttleLeaveDelayDescHidden>The trade shuttle will leave in {0}.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.QuestPartShuttleLeaveDelayDescHidden>

    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.RenegotiateTrade>Renegotiate trade agreement</RealisticOrbitalTrade.RenegotiateTrade>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.OldTradeNonRenegotiable>(only trades made after renegotiation was added to the mod can be renegotiated)</RealisticOrbitalTrade.OldTradeNonRenegotiable>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.DidYouMeanToCancel>You've set all exchange of goods to zero. Did you intend to cancel the trade rather than renegotiate?</RealisticOrbitalTrade.DidYouMeanToCancel>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.NegotiatorTradeDialogInfo>Original negotiator: {0} (+{1})</RealisticOrbitalTrade.NegotiatorTradeDialogInfo>
    <RealisticOrbitalTrade.RenegotiationWarning>I've done my very best to test this feature thoroughly, but it is quite complex, so I might have missed some detail or messed up somewhere. I strongly recommend you save your game each time before you use this feature until you've convinced yourself it works 100% correctly. If you encounter any unexpected or incorrect behavior I would very much appreciate it if you reported it to me.\n\nIf you choose "Confirm" below, this message will not show again.</RealisticOrbitalTrade.RenegotiationWarning>
</LanguageData>
